ALL RIGHT, SO
WE ARE HERE
WITH THE ONE
AND THE ONLY
CLAN CLAN HELLO,
CLAN SURE AND
YOU ARE ONE
OF THE CREATORS
OF THE EVENT
TONIGHT. WHAT INSPIRED
YOU TO PUT
ON THIS EVENT?
NUMBER ONE, WE
GOTTA GIVE THANKS
AND PRAISES TO
OUR LORD ALMIGHTY.
NUMBER TWO, WHAT
INSPIRED ME TO
GET THIS EVENT
IS TO BRING
MY COMMUNITY TOGETHER
AND REALLY PERSONALIZE
MY BRAND. MY
BRAND IS GHANI
HU. IT'S AN
EVIL TURN THAT
MEANS KEEP MOVING
FORWARD. AND IT'S
REALLY A COHORT
OF PEOPLE WHO
JUST BELIEVE IN
ASPIRATION TO JUST
KEEP MOVING FORWARD
NO MATTER HOW
HIGH OR LOW
THEY ARE. I
LOVE THAT. KEEP
MOVING FORWARD. YEAH.
AND CAN WE
EXPECT TO SEE
MORE EVENTS LIKE
THIS THIS SUMMER?
FOR SURE. I
WAS BORN IN
JULY, SO I'D
LOVE TO HAVE
AN EVENT IN
THE SPRING. SO
DEFINITELY EXPECT TO
SEE US SOON.
ON YOUR TIMELINES,
YOUR FEED, YOUR
STORIES, YOUR TIKTOKS
AND EVERYTHING. WE
HAVE AN EVENT
COMING UP IN
JUNE. I CAN'T
WAIT TO TELL
YOU SO MUCH
ABOUT IT. HOPEFULLY
I CAN SEE
ALL THE DETAILS.
Y 'ALL COULD
COME AND INTERVIEW
ME AGAIN BECAUSE
IT'S THE ONLY
OTHER THING FROM
HERE. AND THIS
IS OUR SECOND
GAME NIGHT. I'M
GONNA GIVE YOU
SOME HONEST SCENES.
THE FIRST GAME
NIGHT, WE PROMOTED
FOR THREE WEEKS.
THIS GAME NIGHT,
WE PROMOTED FOR
LIKE NINE DAYS.
AND WE HAVE
A DOUBLE AMOUNT
OF PEOPLE WE
HAVE WITH THAT
AMOUNT OF SPACE.
SO EXPECT THE
NEXT EVENT TO
GZB SPONTANEOUS. IT
MIGHT BE HERE.
IT MIGHT NOT
BE HERE. IT
MIGHT BE WHERE
YOU ARE. YOU
KNOW WHAT I'M
SAYING? BUT MAKE
SURE YOU COME
THERE. IT'S A
FREE EVENT. COME
CHECK US OUT.
COME THROUGH THE
EXPERIENCE. YOU KNOW,
COME CHECK OUR
COMMUNITY OUT. AND
WE ARE PLACED
FOR YOU. NO
MATTER IF YOU
ARE HISPANIC. NEXT
GAME, SHORT, TALL,
BLACK, WHITE. WE
GOT PEOPLE FOR
YOU. AND WE
HERE FOR YOU.
WE'RE EXCITED. SO
STAY TUNED. AND
SEE YOU IN
THE SUMMER. YEAH.